	label	tagged_in_context	span_bounds	all_tokens	all_pos_tokens	all_ner_tokens	silver_tagged_in_context
0	not_propaganda	No, <BOS> he <EOS> will not be confirmed.	(2, 2)	['No', ',', 'he', 'will', 'not', 'be', 'confirmed', '.']	['DT', ',', 'PRP', 'MD', 'RB', 'VB', 'VBN', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	
2	flag_waving	"""The Obama administration misled the <BOS> American people <EOS> and Congress because they were desperate to get a deal with Iran,"" said Sen."	(6, 7)	"['``', 'The', 'Obama', 'administration', 'misled', 'the', 'American', 'people', 'and', 'Congress', 'because', 'they', 'were', 'desperate', 'to', 'get', 'a', 'deal', 'with', 'Iran', ',', ""''"", 'said', 'Sen', '.']"	"['``', 'DT', 'NNP', 'NN', 'VBD', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'CC', 'NNP', 'IN', 'PRP', 'VBD', 'JJ', 'TO', 'VB', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'NNP', ',', ""''"", 'VBD', 'NNP', '.']"	['O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'NORP', 'O', 'O', 'ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'GPE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O']	"""The Obama administration misled the  <BOS> the American people <EOS>  and Congress because they were desperate to get a deal with Iran,"" said Sen."
3	not_propaganda	"""It looks like we're capturing the demise of this dark vortex, <BOS> and <EOS> it's different from what well-known studies led us to expect,"" said Michael H. Wong of the University of California at Berkeley says."	(14, 14)	"['``', 'It', 'looks', 'like', 'we', ""'re"", 'capturing', 'the', 'demise', 'of', 'this', 'dark', 'vortex', ',', 'and', 'it', ""'s"", 'different', 'from', 'what', 'well-known', 'studies', 'led', 'us', 'to', 'expect', ',', ""''"", 'said', 'Michael', 'H.', 'Wong', 'of', 'the', 'University', 'of', 'California', 'at', 'Berkeley', 'says', '.']"	"['``', 'PRP', 'VBZ', 'IN', 'PRP', 'VBP', 'VBG', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', ',', 'CC', 'PRP', 'VBZ', 'JJ', 'IN', 'WP', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'VBD', 'PRP', 'TO', 'VB', ',', ""''"", 'VBD', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'IN', 'DT', 'NNP', 'IN', 'NNP', 'IN', 'NNP', 'VBZ', '.']"	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'O', 'O']	
4	not_propaganda	<BOS> Location: Westerville, Ohio <EOS>	(0, 4)	['Location', ':', 'Westerville', ',', 'Ohio']	['NN', ':', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP']	['O', 'O', 'GPE', 'O', 'GPE']	
5	loaded_language	Hitler <BOS> annihilated <EOS> 400,000 Germans who were handicapped or suffered from chronic diseases.	(1, 1)	['Hitler', 'annihilated', '400,000', 'Germans', 'who', 'were', 'handicapped', 'or', 'suffered', 'from', 'chronic', 'diseases', '.']	['NNP', 'VBD', 'CD', 'NNPS', 'WP', 'VBD', 'VBN', 'CC', 'VBN', 'IN', 'JJ', 'NNS', '.']	['PERSON', 'O', 'CARDINAL', 'NORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	Hitler  <BOS> Eliminated <EOS>  400,000 Germans who were handicapped or suffered from chronic diseases.
6	not_propaganda	A federal judge on Monday ordered U.S. immigration officials to delay any efforts to deport 51 Indonesians living illegally in New Hampshire so the group can have time <BOS> to argue that changing conditions in that country would make it dangerous to return... Federal law gives authority over immigration matters to the executive <EOS> branch, not the courts.	(28, 52)	['A', 'federal', 'judge', 'on', 'Monday', 'ordered', 'U.S.', 'immigration', 'officials', 'to', 'delay', 'any', 'efforts', 'to', 'deport', '51', 'Indonesians', 'living', 'illegally', 'in', 'New', 'Hampshire', 'so', 'the', 'group', 'can', 'have', 'time', 'to', 'argue', 'that', 'changing', 'conditions', 'in', 'that', 'country', 'would', 'make', 'it', 'dangerous', 'to', 'return', '...', 'Federal', 'law', 'gives', 'authority', 'over', 'immigration', 'matters', 'to', 'the', 'executive', 'branch', ',', 'not', 'the', 'courts', '.']	['DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'IN', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'NNP', 'NN', 'NNS', 'TO', 'VB', 'DT', 'NNS', 'TO', 'VB', 'CD', 'NNPS', 'VBG', 'RB', 'IN', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'MD', 'VB', 'NN', 'TO', 'VB', 'IN', 'VBG', 'NNS', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'MD', 'VB', 'PRP', 'JJ', 'TO', 'VB', ':', 'NNP', 'NN', 'VBZ', 'NN', 'IN', 'NN', 'NNS', 'TO', 'DT', 'NN', 'NN', ',', 'RB', 'DT', 'NNS', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'DATE', 'O', 'GPE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'CARDINAL', 'NORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'GPE', 'GPE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	
7	not_propaganda	<BOS> Kirstjen Nielsen (@SecNielsen) <EOS> November 19, 2018	(0, 5)	['Kirstjen', 'Nielsen', '(', '@', 'SecNielsen', ')', 'November', '19', ',', '2018']	['NNP', 'NNP', '(', 'NNP', 'NNP', ')', 'NNP', 'CD', ',', 'CD']	['ORG', 'ORG', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'DATE']	
9	not_propaganda	"Britain doesn't need more hate even just for a <BOS> few days."" <EOS>"	(10, 13)	"['Britain', 'does', ""n't"", 'need', 'more', 'hate', 'even', 'just', 'for', 'a', 'few', 'days', '.', ""''""]"	"['NNP', 'VBZ', 'RB', 'VB', 'JJR', 'JJ', 'RB', 'RB', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NNS', '.', ""''""]"	['GPE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'O', 'O']	
10	name_calling,labeling	"His account was suspended for violating Twitter's rules relating to ""<BOS> hateful conduct <EOS>."" It is ""hateful conduct"", apparently, to reference what Islamic texts themselves say."	(12, 13)	"['His', 'account', 'was', 'suspended', 'for', 'violating', 'Twitter', ""'s"", 'rules', 'relating', 'to', '``', 'hateful', 'conduct', '.', ""''"", 'It', 'is', '``', 'hateful', 'conduct', ""''"", ',', 'apparently', ',', 'to', 'reference', 'what', 'Islamic', 'texts', 'themselves', 'say', '.']"	"['PRP$', 'NN', 'VBD', 'VBN', 'IN', 'VBG', 'NNP', 'POS', 'NNS', 'VBG', 'TO', '``', 'JJ', 'NN', '.', ""''"", 'PRP', 'VBZ', '``', 'JJ', 'NN', ""''"", ',', 'RB', ',', 'TO', 'VB', 'WP', 'NNP', 'NN', 'PRP', 'VBP', '.']"	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'NORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	"His account was suspended for violating Twitter's rules relating to "" <BOS> ""Religious text references"" <EOS> ."" It is ""hateful conduct"", apparently, to reference what Islamic texts themselves say."
11	not_propaganda	Ironically, even in doing this he is <BOS> likely to fail to <EOS> satisfy Muslims, or anyone.	(8, 11)	['Ironically', ',', 'even', 'in', 'doing', 'this', 'he', 'is', 'likely', 'to', 'fail', 'to', 'satisfy', 'Muslims', ',', 'or', 'anyone', '.']	['RB', ',', 'RB', 'IN', 'VBG', 'DT', 'PRP', 'VBZ', 'JJ', 'TO', 'VB', 'TO', 'VB', 'NNP', ',', 'CC', 'NN', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'NORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	
12	appeal_to_fear_prejudice	A couple of seemingly unrelated events this past week <BOS> point to Iran's positioning itself for more aggressive military actions that could place U.S. forces in harm's way <EOS>.	(9, 28)	"['A', 'couple', 'of', 'seemingly', 'unrelated', 'events', 'this', 'past', 'week', 'point', 'to', 'Iran', ""'s"", 'positioning', 'itself', 'for', 'more', 'aggressive', 'military', 'actions', 'that', 'could', 'place', 'U.S.', 'forces', 'in', 'harm', ""'s"", 'way', '.']"	['DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'RB', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'NN', 'TO', 'NNP', 'POS', 'VBG', 'PRP', 'IN', 'RBR', 'JJ', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'WDT', 'MD', 'VB', 'NNP', 'NNS', 'IN', 'NN', 'POS', 'NN', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'O', 'O', 'GPE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'GPE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	A couple of seemingly unrelated events this past week  <BOS> Iran's military buildup may be a sign of a more aggressive stance <EOS> .
15	not_propaganda	"President Trump ordered that the relevant documents be released by the Office of the Director of National Intelligence (ODNI) and the Justice Department ""[a]t the request of a number of committees of Congress, and for <BOS> reasons of transparency,"" read a statement issued by White House <EOS> Press Secretary Sarah Huckabee Sanders."	(42, 53)	"['President', 'Trump', 'ordered', 'that', 'the', 'relevant', 'documents', 'be', 'released', 'by', 'the', 'Office', 'of', 'the', 'Director', 'of', 'National', 'Intelligence', '(', 'ODNI', ')', 'and', 'the', 'Justice', 'Department', '``', '[', 'a', ']', 't', 'the', 'request', 'of', 'a', 'number', 'of', 'committees', 'of', 'Congress', ',', 'and', 'for', 'reasons', 'of', 'transparency', ',', ""''"", 'read', 'a', 'statement', 'issued', 'by', 'White', 'House', 'Press', 'Secretary', 'Sarah', 'Huckabee', 'Sanders', '.']"	"['NNP', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'VB', 'VBN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NNP', 'IN', 'DT', 'NNP', 'IN', 'NNP', 'NNP', '(', 'NNP', ')', 'CC', 'DT', 'NNP', 'NNP', '``', 'VBD', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'NNS', 'IN', 'NNP', ',', 'CC', 'IN', 'NNS', 'IN', 'NN', ',', ""''"", 'VBD', 'DT', 'NN', 'VBN', 'IN', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', '.']"	['O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'O', 'O', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O']	
16	not_propaganda	The newspaper added that Manafort's visit was <BOS> not <EOS> entered into the embassy's log book and cited a source as saying Manafort left after 40 minutes.	(8, 8)	"['The', 'newspaper', 'added', 'that', 'Manafort', ""'s"", 'visit', 'was', 'not', 'entered', 'into', 'the', 'embassy', ""'s"", 'log', 'book', 'and', 'cited', 'a', 'source', 'as', 'saying', 'Manafort', 'left', 'after', '40', 'minutes', '.']"	['DT', 'NN', 'VBD', 'IN', 'NNP', 'POS', 'NN', 'VBD', 'RB', 'VBN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'POS', 'NN', 'NN', 'CC', 'VBD', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'VBG', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'IN', 'CD', 'NNS', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'TIME', 'TIME', 'O']	
17	not_propaganda	"""We are now doing a <BOS> recount, so <EOS> we want to make sure you let your vote be counted,"" Dixon quoted from the voicemail."	(6, 8)	"['``', 'We', 'are', 'now', 'doing', 'a', 'recount', ',', 'so', 'we', 'want', 'to', 'make', 'sure', 'you', 'let', 'your', 'vote', 'be', 'counted', ',', ""''"", 'Dixon', 'quoted', 'from', 'the', 'voicemail', '.']"	"['``', 'PRP', 'VBP', 'RB', 'VBG', 'DT', 'NN', ',', 'IN', 'PRP', 'VBP', 'TO', 'VB', 'JJ', 'PRP', 'VB', 'PRP$', 'NN', 'VB', 'VBN', ',', ""''"", 'NNP', 'VBD', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', '.']"	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	
18	doubt	<BOS> But who authorized this strategic commitment <EOS>, of indefinite duration, in Syria, when near two decades in Afghanistan have failed to secure that nation against the return of al-Qaida and ISIS?	(0, 5)	['But', 'who', 'authorized', 'this', 'strategic', 'commitment', ',', 'of', 'indefinite', 'duration', ',', 'in', 'Syria', ',', 'when', 'near', 'two', 'decades', 'in', 'Afghanistan', 'have', 'failed', 'to', 'secure', 'that', 'nation', 'against', 'the', 'return', 'of', 'al-Qaida', 'and', 'ISIS', '?']	['CC', 'WP', 'VBD', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', ',', 'IN', 'JJ', 'NN', ',', 'IN', 'NNP', ',', 'WRB', 'IN', 'CD', 'NNS', 'IN', 'NNP', 'VBP', 'VBN', 'TO', 'VB', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'JJ', 'CC', 'NNP', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'GPE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'O', 'GPE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'GPE', 'O', 'ORG', 'O']	 <BOS> But who made this strategic commitment a priority? <EOS> , of indefinite duration, in Syria, when near two decades in Afghanistan have failed to secure that nation against the return of al-Qaida and ISIS?
19	causal_oversimplification	Outside of specialists and seekers, <BOS> the only reason why there is general interest in the Qur'an among non-Muslims is to seek an answer to the question of whether or not it justifies and encourages Islamic terrorism <EOS>.	(6, 36)	"['Outside', 'of', 'specialists', 'and', 'seekers', ',', 'the', 'only', 'reason', 'why', 'there', 'is', 'general', 'interest', 'in', 'the', ""Qur'an"", 'among', 'non-Muslims', 'is', 'to', 'seek', 'an', 'answer', 'to', 'the', 'question', 'of', 'whether', 'or', 'not', 'it', 'justifies', 'and', 'encourages', 'Islamic', 'terrorism', '.']"	['IN', 'IN', 'NNS', 'CC', 'NNS', ',', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'WRB', 'EX', 'VBZ', 'JJ', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NNP', 'IN', 'JJ', 'VBZ', 'TO', 'VB', 'DT', 'NN', 'TO', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'IN', 'CC', 'RB', 'PRP', 'VBZ', 'CC', 'VBZ', 'NNP', 'NN', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'GPE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'NORP', 'O', 'O']	Outside of specialists and seekers,  <BOS> the widespread focus on the Qur'an among non-Muslims stems from a desire to gauge its potential impact on Islamic extremism <EOS> .
20	doubt	<BOS> We must ask ourselves why this hasn't happened <EOS>.	(0, 8)	"['We', 'must', 'ask', 'ourselves', 'why', 'this', 'has', ""n't"", 'happened', '.']"	['PRP', 'MD', 'VB', 'PRP', 'WRB', 'DT', 'VBZ', 'RB', 'VBN', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	 <BOS> We must query the reasons behind this inaction <EOS> .
21	loaded_language	We've caught on to his <BOS> sneaky <EOS> synodal tactics.	(6, 6)	"['We', ""'ve"", 'caught', 'on', 'to', 'his', 'sneaky', 'synodal', 'tactics', '.']"	['PRP', 'VBP', 'VBN', 'IN', 'TO', 'PRP$', 'JJ', 'JJ', 'NNS', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	We've caught on to his  <BOS> underhanded synodal tactics <EOS>  synodal tactics.
22	flag_waving	"This is an outrage, but it is common nationwide: the Daily Caller News Foundation reports that Mountain Ridge Middle School in West Virginia is ""instructing junior high students to write the Islamic profession of faith ostensibly to practice calligraphy."" Students are made to write out the Shahada, which states: ""There is no god but Allah, and Muhammad is the messenger of Allah.""This is exactly what I warned about in my book, Stop the Islamization of <BOS> America <EOS>: A Practical Guide to the Resistance , in the chapter ""The Mosqueing of the Public Schools.""In order to convert to Islam, one says the shahada."	(88, 88)	"['This', 'is', 'an', 'outrage', ',', 'but', 'it', 'is', 'common', 'nationwide', ':', 'the', 'Daily', 'Caller', 'News', 'Foundation', 'reports', 'that', 'Mountain', 'Ridge', 'Middle', 'School', 'in', 'West', 'Virginia', 'is', '``', 'instructing', 'junior', 'high', 'students', 'to', 'write', 'the', 'Islamic', 'profession', 'of', 'faith', 'ostensibly', 'to', 'practice', 'calligraphy', '.', ""''"", 'Students', 'are', 'made', 'to', 'write', 'out', 'the', 'Shahada', ',', 'which', 'states', ':', '``', 'There', 'is', 'no', 'god', 'but', 'Allah', ',', 'and', 'Muhammad', 'is', 'the', 'messenger', 'of', 'Allah', '.', '``', 'This', 'is', 'exactly', 'what', 'I', 'warned', 'about', 'in', 'my', 'book', ',', 'Stop', 'the', 'Islamization', 'of', 'America', ':', 'A', 'Practical', 'Guide', 'to', 'the', 'Resistance', ',', 'in', 'the', 'chapter', '``', 'The', 'Mosqueing', 'of', 'the', 'Public', 'Schools', '.', '``', 'In', 'order', 'to', 'convert', 'to', 'Islam', ',', 'one', 'says', 'the', 'shahada', '.']"	"['DT', 'VBZ', 'DT', 'NN', ',', 'CC', 'PRP', 'VBZ', 'JJ', 'JJ', ':', 'DT', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'VBZ', 'IN', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'IN', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'VBZ', '``', 'VBG', 'RB', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'TO', 'VB', 'DT', 'NNP', 'NN', 'IN', 'NN', 'RB', 'TO', 'NN', 'NN', '.', ""''"", 'NNS', 'VBP', 'VBN', 'TO', 'VB', 'RP', 'DT', 'NNP', ',', 'WDT', 'VBZ', ':', '``', 'EX', 'VBZ', 'DT', 'NN', 'CC', 'NNP', ',', 'CC', 'NNP', 'VBZ', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'NNP', '.', '``', 'DT', 'VBZ', 'RB', 'WP', 'PRP', 'VBD', 'IN', 'IN', 'PRP$', 'NN', ',', 'NNP', 'DT', 'NNP', 'IN', 'NNP', ':', 'DT', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'TO', 'DT', 'NNP', ',', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', '``', 'DT', 'NNP', 'IN', 'DT', 'NNP', 'NNP', '.', '``', 'IN', 'NN', 'TO', 'VB', 'TO', 'NNP', ',', 'CD', 'VBZ', 'DT', 'NN', '.']"	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'O', 'O', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'O', 'GPE', 'GPE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'NORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	"This is an outrage, but it is common nationwide: the Daily Caller News Foundation reports that Mountain Ridge Middle School in West Virginia is ""instructing junior high students to write the Islamic profession of faith ostensibly to practice calligraphy."" Students are made to write out the Shahada, which states: ""There is no god but Allah, and Muhammad is the messenger of Allah.""This is exactly what I warned about in my book, Stop the Islamization of  <BOS> Shahada <EOS> : A Practical Guide to the Resistance , in the chapter ""The Mosqueing of the Public Schools.""In order to convert to Islam, one says the shahada."
23	not_propaganda	This <BOS> is the point about the McCarrick scandal that even <EOS> religious commentators tend to overlook.	(1, 9)	['This', 'is', 'the', 'point', 'about', 'the', 'McCarrick', 'scandal', 'that', 'even', 'religious', 'commentators', 'tend', 'to', 'overlook', '.']	['DT', 'VBZ', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NNP', 'NN', 'WDT', 'RB', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'VBP', 'TO', 'VB', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	
24	not_propaganda	Kavanaugh denies the <BOS> accusations. <EOS>	(3, 4)	['Kavanaugh', 'denies', 'the', 'accusations', '.']	['NNP', 'VBZ', 'DT', 'NNS', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	
25	not_propaganda	The time limit of the Commission's members was allowed to lapse without renewal and though it was not dissolved <BOS> formally the Commission has <EOS> ceased to function with no word of any plan to revive it.	(20, 23)	"['The', 'time', 'limit', 'of', 'the', 'Commission', ""'s"", 'members', 'was', 'allowed', 'to', 'lapse', 'without', 'renewal', 'and', 'though', 'it', 'was', 'not', 'dissolved', 'formally', 'the', 'Commission', 'has', 'ceased', 'to', 'function', 'with', 'no', 'word', 'of', 'any', 'plan', 'to', 'revive', 'it', '.']"	['DT', 'NN', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NNP', 'POS', 'NNS', 'VBD', 'VBN', 'TO', 'VB', 'IN', 'NN', 'CC', 'IN', 'PRP', 'VBD', 'RB', 'VBN', 'RB', 'DT', 'NNP', 'VBZ', 'VBN', 'TO', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'TO', 'VB', 'PRP', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	
26	name_calling,labeling	"Bob Mueller is totally conflicted, and his 17 Angry Democrats that are doing his dirty work are <BOS> a disgrace to USA <EOS>!"" Trump wrote."	(18, 21)	"['Bob', 'Mueller', 'is', 'totally', 'conflicted', ',', 'and', 'his', '17', 'Angry', 'Democrats', 'that', 'are', 'doing', 'his', 'dirty', 'work', 'are', 'a', 'disgrace', 'to', 'USA', '!', ""''"", 'Trump', 'wrote', '.']"	"['NNP', 'NNP', 'VBZ', 'RB', 'VBN', ',', 'CC', 'PRP$', 'CD', 'JJ', 'NNPS', 'WDT', 'VBP', 'VBG', 'PRP$', 'NN', 'NN', 'VBP', 'DT', 'NN', 'TO', 'VB', '.', ""''"", 'NNP', 'VBD', '.']"	['PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'CARDINAL', 'O', 'NORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'GPE', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O']	"Bob Mueller is totally conflicted, and his 17 Angry Democrats that are doing his dirty work are  <BOS> an embarrassment to the United States <EOS> !"" Trump wrote."
27	not_propaganda	"""Let me get this straight: this is [a] statement about [a] secret letter regarding a secret matter and an <BOS> unidentified person. <EOS>"	(25, 27)	['``', 'Let', 'me', 'get', 'this', 'straight', ':', 'this', 'is', '[', 'a', ']', 'statement', 'about', '[', 'a', ']', 'secret', 'letter', 'regarding', 'a', 'secret', 'matter', 'and', 'an', 'unidentified', 'person', '.']	['``', 'VB', 'PRP', 'VB', 'DT', 'NN', ':', 'DT', 'VBZ', 'VBZ', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'IN', 'PDT', 'DT', 'NN', 'JJ', 'NN', 'VBG', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'CC', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	
28	not_propaganda	Average age: <BOS> 65 <EOS>	(3, 3)	['Average', 'age', ':', '65']	['JJ', 'NN', ':', 'CD']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'CARDINAL']	
29	not_propaganda	Present problems: ageing of the <BOS> sisters and a lack of <EOS> vocations.	(6, 10)	['Present', 'problems', ':', 'ageing', 'of', 'the', 'sisters', 'and', 'a', 'lack', 'of', 'vocations', '.']	['JJ', 'NNS', ':', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NNS', 'CC', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'NNS', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	
30	not_propaganda	He stood up to challenge <BOS> the fact that the CIA was about to <EOS> hand over leadership to a person who had been in charge of torture.	(5, 12)	['He', 'stood', 'up', 'to', 'challenge', 'the', 'fact', 'that', 'the', 'CIA', 'was', 'about', 'to', 'hand', 'over', 'leadership', 'to', 'a', 'person', 'who', 'had', 'been', 'in', 'charge', 'of', 'torture', '.']	['PRP', 'VBD', 'RP', 'TO', 'VB', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'IN', 'TO', 'NN', 'RP', 'NN', 'TO', 'DT', 'NN', 'WP', 'VBD', 'VBN', 'IN', 'NN', 'IN', 'NN', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	
31	repetition	Hitler embodies one type of modern Western <BOS> annihilation <EOS>.	(7, 7)	['Hitler', 'embodies', 'one', 'type', 'of', 'modern', 'Western', 'annihilation', '.']	['NNP', 'VBZ', 'CD', 'NN', 'IN', 'JJ', 'JJ', 'NN', '.']	['PERSON', 'O', 'CARDINAL', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	Hitler embodies one type of modern Western  <BOS> Totalitarian <EOS> .
32	not_propaganda	He was previously removed to Mexico in 2009 after he illegally entered the United States through Laredo, <BOS> Texas. <EOS>	(18, 19)	['He', 'was', 'previously', 'removed', 'to', 'Mexico', 'in', '2009', 'after', 'he', 'illegally', 'entered', 'the', 'United', 'States', 'through', 'Laredo', ',', 'Texas', '.']	['PRP', 'VBD', 'RB', 'VBN', 'TO', 'NNP', 'IN', 'CD', 'IN', 'PRP', 'RB', 'VBD', 'DT', 'NNP', 'NNPS', 'IN', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'GPE', 'O', 'DATE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'GPE', 'GPE', 'GPE', 'O', 'GPE', 'O', 'GPE', 'O']	
34	repetition	Kritarch Saris thought she knew better and has been running a deliberate campaign to prevent the deportation of these Chinese <BOS> illegal aliens <EOS>.	(20, 21)	['Kritarch', 'Saris', 'thought', 'she', 'knew', 'better', 'and', 'has', 'been', 'running', 'a', 'deliberate', 'campaign', 'to', 'prevent', 'the', 'deportation', 'of', 'these', 'Chinese', 'illegal', 'aliens', '.']	['NNP', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'PRP', 'VBD', 'RBR', 'CC', 'VBZ', 'VBN', 'VBG', 'DT', 'NN', 'NN', 'TO', 'VB', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'JJ', 'NNS', '.']	['PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'NORP', 'O', 'O', 'O']	Kritarch Saris thought she knew better and has been running a deliberate campaign to prevent the deportation of these Chinese  <BOS> indigenous Chinese nationals <EOS> .
35	repetition	But now, the <BOS> sonic attacks <EOS> have progressed beyond Cuba.	(4, 5)	['But', 'now', ',', 'the', 'sonic', 'attacks', 'have', 'progressed', 'beyond', 'Cuba', '.']	['CC', 'RB', ',', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'VBP', 'VBN', 'IN', 'NNP', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'GPE', 'O']	But now, the  <BOS> International broadcasts <EOS>  have progressed beyond Cuba.
37	not_propaganda	(The Dutch media now claim that one of them doesn't depict <BOS> Muslim <EOS> migrants being violent, as was claimed.	(13, 13)	"['(', 'The', 'Dutch', 'media', 'now', 'claim', 'that', 'one', 'of', 'them', 'does', ""n't"", 'depict', 'Muslim', 'migrants', 'being', 'violent', ',', 'as', 'was', 'claimed', '.']"	['(', 'DT', 'NNPS', 'NNS', 'RB', 'VBP', 'IN', 'CD', 'IN', 'PRP', 'VBZ', 'RB', 'VB', 'NNP', 'NNS', 'VBG', 'JJ', ',', 'IN', 'VBD', 'VBN', '.']	['O', 'O', 'NORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'CARDINAL', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'NORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	
38	appeal_to_fear_prejudice	<BOS> Either you stand with BDS, Hamas, blood libels and those who want to destroy Israel or with Jews <EOS>.	(0, 19)	['Either', 'you', 'stand', 'with', 'BDS', ',', 'Hamas', ',', 'blood', 'libels', 'and', 'those', 'who', 'want', 'to', 'destroy', 'Israel', 'or', 'with', 'Jews', '.']	['CC', 'PRP', 'VBP', 'IN', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', ',', 'NN', 'NNS', 'CC', 'DT', 'WP', 'VBP', 'TO', 'VB', 'NNP', 'CC', 'IN', 'NNPS', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORG', 'O', 'ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'GPE', 'O', 'O', 'NORP', 'O']	 <BOS> Let's avoid hate speech and prejudice, and focus on respectful and productive conversations <EOS> .
39	appeal_to_fear_prejudice	<BOS> Putting aside freedom of speech, the persecution of this man has been something that should horrify all free-thinking people. If it doesn't horrify us, then we have surrendered something very valuable <EOS>.	(0, 34)	"['Putting', 'aside', 'freedom', 'of', 'speech', ',', 'the', 'persecution', 'of', 'this', 'man', 'has', 'been', 'something', 'that', 'should', 'horrify', 'all', 'free-thinking', 'people', '.', 'If', 'it', 'does', ""n't"", 'horrify', 'us', ',', 'then', 'we', 'have', 'surrendered', 'something', 'very', 'valuable', '.']"	['VBG', 'JJ', 'NN', 'IN', 'NN', ',', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'VBZ', 'VBN', 'NN', 'WDT', 'MD', 'VB', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NNS', '.', 'IN', 'PRP', 'VBZ', 'RB', 'VB', 'PRP', ',', 'RB', 'PRP', 'VBP', 'VBN', 'NN', 'RB', 'JJ', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	 <BOS> Putting aside the significance of free speech, the plight of this individual is a stark reminder of the dangers of oppression. If it doesn't unsettle us, then we have succumbed to the erosion of our values <EOS> .
40	not_propaganda	She <BOS> is <EOS> calling for an Israeli/Palestinian state that would not be a Jewish State or a homeland for the Jewish people, but a federation in which Palestinians would soon overwhelm Jews demographically.	(1, 1)	['She', 'is', 'calling', 'for', 'an', 'Israeli/Palestinian', 'state', 'that', 'would', 'not', 'be', 'a', 'Jewish', 'State', 'or', 'a', 'homeland', 'for', 'the', 'Jewish', 'people', ',', 'but', 'a', 'federation', 'in', 'which', 'Palestinians', 'would', 'soon', 'overwhelm', 'Jews', 'demographically', '.']	['PRP', 'VBZ', 'VBG', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'WDT', 'MD', 'RB', 'VB', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NNP', 'CC', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NNS', ',', 'CC', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'WDT', 'NNPS', 'MD', 'RB', 'VB', 'NNP', 'RB', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'NORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'NORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'NORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'NORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'NORP', 'O', 'O']	
41	not_propaganda	"""Motive a mystery in car explosion at Travis Air Force Base,"" by Phil Willon, Los Angeles Times, March 23, <BOS> 2018: <EOS>"	(25, 26)	"['``', 'Motive', 'a', 'mystery', 'in', 'car', 'explosion', 'at', 'Travis', 'Air', 'Force', 'Base', ',', ""''"", 'by', 'Phil', 'Willon', ',', 'Los', 'Angeles', 'Times', ',', 'March', '23', ',', '2018', ':']"	"['``', 'VB', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'NN', 'NN', 'IN', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', ""''"", 'IN', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'CD', ',', 'CD', ':']"	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'FAC', 'FAC', 'FAC', 'FAC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'O', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'O']	
42	causal_oversimplification	"Whosoever shall shed man's blood, his blood shall be shed: for man was made to the image of God."" In other words, <BOS> from that point in history lawful killing in atonement for taking the life of another is sanctioned by God <EOS>."	(28, 46)	"['Whosoever', 'shall', 'shed', 'man', ""'s"", 'blood', ',', 'his', 'blood', 'shall', 'be', 'shed', ':', 'for', 'man', 'was', 'made', 'to', 'the', 'image', 'of', 'God', '.', ""''"", 'In', 'other', 'words', ',', 'from', 'that', 'point', 'in', 'history', 'lawful', 'killing', 'in', 'atonement', 'for', 'taking', 'the', 'life', 'of', 'another', 'is', 'sanctioned', 'by', 'God', '.']"	"['NNP', 'MD', 'VB', 'NN', 'POS', 'NN', ',', 'PRP$', 'NN', 'MD', 'VB', 'VBN', ':', 'IN', 'NN', 'VBD', 'VBN', 'TO', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'NNP', '.', ""''"", 'IN', 'JJ', 'NNS', ',', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'NN', 'JJ', 'NN', 'IN', 'NN', 'IN', 'VBG', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'VBZ', 'VBN', 'IN', 'NNP', '.']"	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	"Whosoever shall shed man's blood, his blood shall be shed: for man was made to the image of God."" In other words,  <BOS> From that point in history, God's decree ordained the act of killing in atonement for taking the life of another <EOS> ."
44	flag_waving	Thanks to President Trump and the CIA's decision <BOS> to continue keeping 98 percent of the CIA's decades-long secret records secret from the American people <EOS>, the CIA's cunning cover-up of the JFK assassination continues to work brilliantly today.	(9, 25)	"['Thanks', 'to', 'President', 'Trump', 'and', 'the', 'CIA', ""'s"", 'decision', 'to', 'continue', 'keeping', '98', 'percent', 'of', 'the', 'CIA', ""'s"", 'decades-long', 'secret', 'records', 'secret', 'from', 'the', 'American', 'people', ',', 'the', 'CIA', ""'s"", 'cunning', 'cover-up', 'of', 'the', 'JFK', 'assassination', 'continues', 'to', 'work', 'brilliantly', 'today', '.']"	['NNS', 'TO', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'CC', 'DT', 'NNP', 'POS', 'NN', 'TO', 'VB', 'VBG', 'CD', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NNP', 'POS', 'JJ', 'NN', 'NNS', 'VBP', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NNS', ',', 'DT', 'NNP', 'POS', 'VBG', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NNP', 'NN', 'VBZ', 'TO', 'VB', 'RB', 'NN', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERCENT', 'PERCENT', 'O', 'O', 'ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'NORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'DATE', 'O']	Thanks to President Trump and the CIA's decision  <BOS> to deceive the American public by concealing 98 percent of the CIA's decades-long classified records <EOS> , the CIA's cunning cover-up of the JFK assassination continues to work brilliantly today.
45	not_propaganda	Frings, Archbishop of <BOS> Cologne. <EOS>	(4, 5)	['Frings', ',', 'Archbishop', 'of', 'Cologne', '.']	['NNS', ',', 'NNP', 'IN', 'NNP', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'GPE', 'O']	
46	flag_waving	Where is that authorized in <BOS> our Constitution <EOS>?	(5, 6)	['Where', 'is', 'that', 'authorized', 'in', 'our', 'Constitution', '?']	['WRB', 'VBZ', 'IN', 'VBN', 'IN', 'PRP$', 'NN', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'LAW', 'O']	Where is that authorized in  <BOS> our constitutional authority <EOS> ?
47	causal_oversimplification	"While the establishment continues to push the notion that <BOS> a couple hundred thousand dollars of ad spends and some Russian bots on Facebook swayed the election to Donald Trump <EOS>, more proof of real ""collusion"" between Google and the Hillary Clinton campaign has been uncovered."	(9, 28)	"['While', 'the', 'establishment', 'continues', 'to', 'push', 'the', 'notion', 'that', 'a', 'couple', 'hundred', 'thousand', 'dollars', 'of', 'ad', 'spends', 'and', 'some', 'Russian', 'bots', 'on', 'Facebook', 'swayed', 'the', 'election', 'to', 'Donald', 'Trump', ',', 'more', 'proof', 'of', 'real', '``', 'collusion', ""''"", 'between', 'Google', 'and', 'the', 'Hillary', 'Clinton', 'campaign', 'has', 'been', 'uncovered', '.']"	"['IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'VBZ', 'TO', 'VB', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'CD', 'CD', 'NNS', 'IN', 'NN', 'NNS', 'CC', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'IN', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'DT', 'NN', 'TO', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'RBR', 'NN', 'IN', 'JJ', '``', 'NN', ""''"", 'IN', 'NNP', 'CC', 'DT', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NN', 'VBZ', 'VBN', 'VBN', '.']"	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'MONEY', 'MONEY', 'MONEY', 'MONEY', 'MONEY', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'NORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORG', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	"While the establishment continues to push the notion that  <BOS> A hefty sum of money spent on advertisements and a multitude of Russian-controlled Facebook accounts contributed to a significant shift in the electoral outcome, ultimately benefiting Donald Trump. <EOS> , more proof of real ""collusion"" between Google and the Hillary Clinton campaign has been uncovered."
48	exaggeration,minimisation	Britain took part in an investigation which determined that Julian was a political refugee and that <BOS> a great miscarriage of justice <EOS> had been imposed on him.	(16, 20)	['Britain', 'took', 'part', 'in', 'an', 'investigation', 'which', 'determined', 'that', 'Julian', 'was', 'a', 'political', 'refugee', 'and', 'that', 'a', 'great', 'miscarriage', 'of', 'justice', 'had', 'been', 'imposed', 'on', 'him', '.']	['NNP', 'VBD', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'WDT', 'VBD', 'IN', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'CC', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'IN', 'NN', 'VBD', 'VBN', 'VBN', 'IN', 'PRP', '.']	['GPE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	Britain took part in an investigation which determined that Julian was a political refugee and that  <BOS> A flawed asylum decision <EOS>  had been imposed on him.
49	loaded_language	"This is why it is so <BOS> heinous <EOS>."""	(6, 6)	"['This', 'is', 'why', 'it', 'is', 'so', 'heinous', '.', ""''""]"	"['DT', 'VBZ', 'WRB', 'PRP', 'VBZ', 'RB', 'JJ', '.', ""''""]"	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	"This is why it is so  <BOS> Atrocious <EOS> ."""
50	causal_oversimplification	<BOS> The last-minute accusations from Christine Blasey Ford, a woman who claims that decades ago Kavanaugh groped her at a high school party, and Deborah Ramirez, who accused Kavanaugh of exposing himself to her at a frat party at Yale, are transparent acts of aggression against the judge and Republicans, one engineered by the Democrats <EOS>.	(0, 58)	['The', 'last-minute', 'accusations', 'from', 'Christine', 'Blasey', 'Ford', ',', 'a', 'woman', 'who', 'claims', 'that', 'decades', 'ago', 'Kavanaugh', 'groped', 'her', 'at', 'a', 'high', 'school', 'party', ',', 'and', 'Deborah', 'Ramirez', ',', 'who', 'accused', 'Kavanaugh', 'of', 'exposing', 'himself', 'to', 'her', 'at', 'a', 'frat', 'party', 'at', 'Yale', ',', 'are', 'transparent', 'acts', 'of', 'aggression', 'against', 'the', 'judge', 'and', 'Republicans', ',', 'one', 'engineered', 'by', 'the', 'Democrats', '.']	['DT', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'IN', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'DT', 'NN', 'WP', 'VBZ', 'IN', 'NNS', 'RB', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'PRP$', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'NN', ',', 'CC', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'WP', 'VBD', 'NNP', 'IN', 'VBG', 'PRP', 'TO', 'PRP$', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'NN', 'IN', 'NNP', ',', 'VBP', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'IN', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'CC', 'NNPS', ',', 'CD', 'VBN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NNPS', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'NORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'NORP', 'O']	 <BOS> The last-minute accusations from Christine Blasey Ford, who claims that Kavanaugh committed sexual misconduct at a high school gathering, and Deborah Ramirez, who accuses him of lewd exposure at a Yale fraternity party, represent a calculated attempt to discredit the judge and Republicans, cleverly engineered by the Democratic Party <EOS> .
51	doubt	"I said that <BOS> the reason I dropped the ""J"" word was because you haven't in 40 years <EOS> (Romans 1:16)."	(3, 19)	"['I', 'said', 'that', 'the', 'reason', 'I', 'dropped', 'the', '``', 'J', ""''"", 'word', 'was', 'because', 'you', 'have', ""n't"", 'in', '40', 'years', '(', 'Romans', '1:16', ')', '.']"	"['PRP', 'VBD', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'PRP', 'VBD', 'DT', '``', 'NNP', ""''"", 'NN', 'VBD', 'IN', 'PRP', 'VBP', 'RB', 'IN', 'CD', 'NNS', '(', 'NNPS', 'CD', ')', '.']"	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'O', 'NORP', 'O', 'O', 'O']	I said that  <BOS> the reason I stopped using the 'N-word' was because you haven't in 40 years. <EOS>  (Romans 1:16).
52	appeal_to_fear_prejudice	"In a letter to the Australian prime minister, Malcolm Turnbull, Julian's father, John Shipton, wrote: ""I ask the prime minister <BOS> to do all within his power to return Julian home before Julian's situation becomes an irreversible tragedy <EOS>."" That is why this is such an urgent case of justice toward a single human being as well as a case of a journalistic organization's right to function and our right to have the information it provides."	(27, 44)	"['In', 'a', 'letter', 'to', 'the', 'Australian', 'prime', 'minister', ',', 'Malcolm', 'Turnbull', ',', 'Julian', ""'s"", 'father', ',', 'John', 'Shipton', ',', 'wrote', ':', '``', 'I', 'ask', 'the', 'prime', 'minister', 'to', 'do', 'all', 'within', 'his', 'power', 'to', 'return', 'Julian', 'home', 'before', 'Julian', ""'s"", 'situation', 'becomes', 'an', 'irreversible', 'tragedy', '.', ""''"", 'That', 'is', 'why', 'this', 'is', 'such', 'an', 'urgent', 'case', 'of', 'justice', 'toward', 'a', 'single', 'human', 'being', 'as', 'well', 'as', 'a', 'case', 'of', 'a', 'journalistic', 'organization', ""'s"", 'right', 'to', 'function', 'and', 'our', 'right', 'to', 'have', 'the', 'information', 'it', 'provides', '.']"	"['IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'TO', 'DT', 'JJ', 'JJ', 'NN', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'POS', 'NN', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'VBD', ':', '``', 'PRP', 'VBP', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'TO', 'VB', 'DT', 'IN', 'PRP$', 'NN', 'TO', 'VB', 'NNP', 'NN', 'IN', 'NNP', 'POS', 'NN', 'VBZ', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', '.', ""''"", 'DT', 'VBZ', 'WRB', 'DT', 'VBZ', 'JJ', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'IN', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'JJ', 'VBG', 'RB', 'RB', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'POS', 'NN', 'TO', 'NN', 'CC', 'PRP$', 'NN', 'TO', 'VB', 'DT', 'NN', 'PRP', 'VBZ', '.']"	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'NORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'NORP', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	"In a letter to the Australian prime minister, Malcolm Turnbull, Julian's father, John Shipton, wrote: ""I ask the prime minister  <BOS> to do everything feasible to prevent Julian's situation from spiraling out of control <EOS> ."" That is why this is such an urgent case of justice toward a single human being as well as a case of a journalistic organization's right to function and our right to have the information it provides."
53	not_propaganda	They practiced <BOS> sauvage <EOS> intercommunion.	(2, 2)	['They', 'practiced', 'sauvage', 'intercommunion', '.']	['PRP', 'VBD', 'NN', 'NN', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	
54	not_propaganda	<BOS> The <EOS> first version read:	(0, 0)	['The', 'first', 'version', 'read', ':']	['DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'NN', ':']	['O', 'ORDINAL', 'O', 'O', 'O']	
56	not_propaganda	Even though Senator Feinstein had the <BOS> letter in hand, she never <EOS> brought up the charge during the public hearing, nor during her own meeting with the judge.	(6, 11)	['Even', 'though', 'Senator', 'Feinstein', 'had', 'the', 'letter', 'in', 'hand', ',', 'she', 'never', 'brought', 'up', 'the', 'charge', 'during', 'the', 'public', 'hearing', ',', 'nor', 'during', 'her', 'own', 'meeting', 'with', 'the', 'judge', '.']	['RB', 'IN', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'NN', ',', 'PRP', 'RB', 'VBD', 'RP', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', ',', 'CC', 'IN', 'PRP$', 'JJ', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	
57	not_propaganda	One hundred thousand <BOS> persons were killed in <EOS> Fez on that occasion, and 120,000 in Marrakesh.	(3, 6)	['One', 'hundred', 'thousand', 'persons', 'were', 'killed', 'in', 'Fez', 'on', 'that', 'occasion', ',', 'and', '120,000', 'in', 'Marrakesh', '.']	['CD', 'CD', 'NN', 'NNS', 'VBD', 'VBN', 'IN', 'NNP', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', ',', 'CC', 'CD', 'IN', 'NNP', '.']	['CARDINAL', 'CARDINAL', 'CARDINAL', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'GPE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'CARDINAL', 'O', 'GPE', 'O']	
58	not_propaganda	Ninety-two percent of individuals removed from the interior of the United States had previously been convicted of a criminal <BOS> offense. <EOS>	(19, 20)	['Ninety-two', 'percent', 'of', 'individuals', 'removed', 'from', 'the', 'interior', 'of', 'the', 'United', 'States', 'had', 'previously', 'been', 'convicted', 'of', 'a', 'criminal', 'offense', '.']	['JJ', 'NN', 'IN', 'NNS', 'VBN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NNP', 'NNPS', 'VBD', 'RB', 'VBN', 'VBN', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'GPE', 'GPE', 'GPE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	
59	name_calling,labeling	<BOS> Deep State DOJ tool <EOS> Rod Rosenstein refuses to comply with Trump's executive order as afforded him by the US Constitution.	(0, 3)	"['Deep', 'State', 'DOJ', 'tool', 'Rod', 'Rosenstein', 'refuses', 'to', 'comply', 'with', 'Trump', ""'s"", 'executive', 'order', 'as', 'afforded', 'him', 'by', 'the', 'US', 'Constitution', '.']"	['JJ', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NN', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'VBZ', 'TO', 'VB', 'IN', 'NNP', 'POS', 'NN', 'NN', 'IN', 'VBD', 'PRP', 'IN', 'DT', 'NNP', 'NNP', '.']	['PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'EVENT', 'EVENT', 'EVENT', 'O']	 <BOS> Cogs in the Beltway Machine <EOS>  Rod Rosenstein refuses to comply with Trump's executive order as afforded him by the US Constitution.
60	not_propaganda	<BOS> Why? <EOS>	(0, 1)	['Why', '?']	['WRB', '.']	['O', 'O']	
61	not_propaganda	As expected, at today's hearing Kavanaugh will firmly <BOS> rebut the increasingly outrageous claims <EOS> being leveled at him.	(10, 14)	"['As', 'expected', ',', 'at', 'today', ""'s"", 'hearing', 'Kavanaugh', 'will', 'firmly', 'rebut', 'the', 'increasingly', 'outrageous', 'claims', 'being', 'leveled', 'at', 'him', '.']"	['IN', 'VBN', ',', 'IN', 'NN', 'POS', 'NN', 'NNP', 'MD', 'VB', 'VB', 'DT', 'RB', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'VBG', 'VBN', 'IN', 'PRP', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'DATE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	
63	name_calling,labeling	In an op-ed published several years ago by The Los Angeles Times, two members of Veteran Intelligence Professionals for Sanity, Coleen Rowley and Bogdan Dzakovic, pointed out that  If WikiLeaks had been up and running before 9/11  <BOS> frustrated FBI investigators <EOS> might have chosen to leak information that their superiors bottled up, perhaps averting the terrorism attacks.	(40, 42)	['In', 'an', 'op-ed', 'published', 'several', 'years', 'ago', 'by', 'The', 'Los', 'Angeles', 'Times', ',', 'two', 'members', 'of', 'Veteran', 'Intelligence', 'Professionals', 'for', 'Sanity', ',', 'Coleen', 'Rowley', 'and', 'Bogdan', 'Dzakovic', ',', 'pointed', 'out', 'that', 'If', 'WikiLeaks', 'had', 'been', 'up', 'and', 'running', 'before', '9/11', 'frustrated', 'FBI', 'investigators', 'might', 'have', 'chosen', 'to', 'leak', 'information', 'that', 'their', 'superiors', 'bottled', 'up', ',', 'perhaps', 'averting', 'the', 'terrorism', 'attacks', '.']	['IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'VBN', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'RB', 'IN', 'DT', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'CD', 'NNS', 'IN', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'IN', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'CC', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'VBD', 'RP', 'IN', 'IN', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'VBN', 'RB', 'CC', 'VBG', 'RB', 'CD', 'JJ', 'NNP', 'NNS', 'MD', 'VB', 'VBN', 'TO', 'VB', 'NN', 'IN', 'PRP$', 'NNS', 'VBD', 'RP', ',', 'RB', 'VBG', 'DT', 'NN', 'NNS', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'O', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'O', 'CARDINAL', 'O', 'O', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'CARDINAL', 'O', 'ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	In an op-ed published several years ago by The Los Angeles Times, two members of Veteran Intelligence Professionals for Sanity, Coleen Rowley and Bogdan Dzakovic, pointed out that  If WikiLeaks had been up and running before 9/11   <BOS> Frustrated intelligence officers <EOS>  might have chosen to leak information that their superiors bottled up, perhaps averting the terrorism attacks.
64	not_propaganda	Simply expressing support for a terrorist organization or attack is <BOS> not against the <EOS> law.	(10, 12)	['Simply', 'expressing', 'support', 'for', 'a', 'terrorist', 'organization', 'or', 'attack', 'is', 'not', 'against', 'the', 'law', '.']	['NNP', 'VBG', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'CC', 'NN', 'VBZ', 'RB', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	
66	not_propaganda	<BOS> In Asia, preserving 'face' is essential. <EOS>	(0, 8)	"['In', 'Asia', ',', 'preserving', ""'face"", ""'"", 'is', 'essential', '.']"	"['IN', 'NNP', ',', 'VBG', 'NN', ""''"", 'VBZ', 'JJ', '.']"	['O', 'LOC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	
67	appeal_to_fear_prejudice	But experts now warn that because they are being used so much to treat the infection, <BOS> antibiotics resistance is inevitable <EOS> and making this disease much more terrifying.	(17, 20)	['But', 'experts', 'now', 'warn', 'that', 'because', 'they', 'are', 'being', 'used', 'so', 'much', 'to', 'treat', 'the', 'infection', ',', 'antibiotics', 'resistance', 'is', 'inevitable', 'and', 'making', 'this', 'disease', 'much', 'more', 'terrifying', '.']	['CC', 'NNS', 'RB', 'VBP', 'IN', 'IN', 'PRP', 'VBP', 'VBG', 'VBN', 'RB', 'JJ', 'TO', 'VB', 'DT', 'NN', ',', 'NNS', 'NN', 'VBZ', 'JJ', 'CC', 'VBG', 'DT', 'NN', 'RB', 'RBR', 'JJ', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	But experts now warn that because they are being used so much to treat the infection,  <BOS> will increase the disease's deadliness <EOS>  and making this disease much more terrifying.
68	not_propaganda	In addition to securing the Gulf, the 5th Fleet serves as a constant <BOS> reminder to the Iranians of <EOS> their impotence.	(14, 18)	['In', 'addition', 'to', 'securing', 'the', 'Gulf', ',', 'the', '5th', 'Fleet', 'serves', 'as', 'a', 'constant', 'reminder', 'to', 'the', 'Iranians', 'of', 'their', 'impotence', '.']	['IN', 'NN', 'TO', 'VBG', 'DT', 'NNP', ',', 'DT', 'CD', 'NNP', 'NNS', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'TO', 'DT', 'NNPS', 'IN', 'PRP$', 'NN', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'LOC', 'O', 'O', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'NORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	
70	name_calling,labeling	"About the clip, on Facebook, Zakkout wrote above it, ""Makes a lot of sense!"" Of course, this is coming from someone [Zakkout] who regularly refers to Jews as ""<BOS> monkeys and pigs <EOS>,"" and in February 2016, circulated on social media a report claiming that ""the Holocaust was faked."" The report calls the Holocaust ""the biggest lie ever foisted upon humanity"" and was produced by a media outlet which describes Hitler as ""the greatest leader in modern Western history."""	(38, 40)	"['About', 'the', 'clip', ',', 'on', 'Facebook', ',', 'Zakkout', 'wrote', 'above', 'it', ',', '``', 'Makes', 'a', 'lot', 'of', 'sense', '!', ""''"", 'Of', 'course', ',', 'this', 'is', 'coming', 'from', 'someone', '[', 'Zakkout', ']', 'who', 'regularly', 'refers', 'to', 'Jews', 'as', '``', 'monkeys', 'and', 'pigs', ',', ""''"", 'and', 'in', 'February', '2016', ',', 'circulated', 'on', 'social', 'media', 'a', 'report', 'claiming', 'that', '``', 'the', 'Holocaust', 'was', 'faked', '.', ""''"", 'The', 'report', 'calls', 'the', 'Holocaust', '``', 'the', 'biggest', 'lie', 'ever', 'foisted', 'upon', 'humanity', ""''"", 'and', 'was', 'produced', 'by', 'a', 'media', 'outlet', 'which', 'describes', 'Hitler', 'as', '``', 'the', 'greatest', 'leader', 'in', 'modern', 'Western', 'history', '.', ""''""]"	"['IN', 'DT', 'NN', ',', 'IN', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'IN', 'PRP', ',', '``', 'VBZ', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'NN', '.', ""''"", 'IN', 'NN', ',', 'DT', 'VBZ', 'VBG', 'IN', 'NN', 'NN', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'WP', 'RB', 'NNS', 'TO', 'VB', 'IN', '``', 'NNS', 'CC', 'NNS', ',', ""''"", 'CC', 'IN', 'NNP', 'CD', ',', 'VBN', 'IN', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'DT', 'NN', 'VBG', 'IN', '``', 'DT', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'VBN', '.', ""''"", 'DT', 'NN', 'VBZ', 'DT', 'NNP', '``', 'DT', 'JJS', 'NN', 'RB', 'VBN', 'IN', 'NN', ""''"", 'CC', 'VBD', 'VBN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NNS', 'NN', 'WDT', 'VBZ', 'NNP', 'IN', '``', 'DT', 'JJS', 'NN', 'IN', 'JJ', 'JJ', 'NN', '.', ""''""]"	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'NORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'NORP', 'O', 'O', 'O']	"About the clip, on Facebook, Zakkout wrote above it, ""Makes a lot of sense!"" Of course, this is coming from someone [Zakkout] who regularly refers to Jews as "" <BOS> ""bigots and swine"" <EOS> ,"" and in February 2016, circulated on social media a report claiming that ""the Holocaust was faked."" The report calls the Holocaust ""the biggest lie ever foisted upon humanity"" and was produced by a media outlet which describes Hitler as ""the greatest leader in modern Western history."""
71	doubt	It's also the case that the more negative information comes out, the more it appears that the <BOS> Trump and his White House staff failed to do their jobs <EOS> in vetting and managing Kavanaugh.	(19, 29)	"['It', ""'s"", 'also', 'the', 'case', 'that', 'the', 'more', 'negative', 'information', 'comes', 'out', ',', 'the', 'more', 'it', 'appears', 'that', 'the', 'Trump', 'and', 'his', 'White', 'House', 'staff', 'failed', 'to', 'do', 'their', 'jobs', 'in', 'vetting', 'and', 'managing', 'Kavanaugh', '.']"	['PRP', 'VBZ', 'RB', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'RBR', 'JJ', 'NN', 'VBZ', 'RP', ',', 'DT', 'JJR', 'PRP', 'VBZ', 'IN', 'DT', 'NNP', 'CC', 'PRP$', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NN', 'VBD', 'TO', 'VB', 'PRP$', 'NNS', 'IN', 'NN', 'CC', 'NN', 'NNP', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	It's also the case that the more negative information comes out, the more it appears that the  <BOS> Trump and his White House staff were slow to respond to the information. <EOS>  in vetting and managing Kavanaugh.
72	causal_oversimplification	<BOS> To eradicate these, Muslims are required to wage war until there exists none of it in the world, and the only religion is that of Allah <EOS>.	(0, 27)	['To', 'eradicate', 'these', ',', 'Muslims', 'are', 'required', 'to', 'wage', 'war', 'until', 'there', 'exists', 'none', 'of', 'it', 'in', 'the', 'world', ',', 'and', 'the', 'only', 'religion', 'is', 'that', 'of', 'Allah', '.']	['TO', 'VB', 'DT', ',', 'NNS', 'VBP', 'VBN', 'TO', 'NN', 'NN', 'IN', 'EX', 'VBZ', 'NN', 'IN', 'PRP', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', ',', 'CC', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'VBZ', 'IN', 'IN', 'NNP', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'NORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	 <BOS> The intricacies of the situation necessitate a more nuanced understanding <EOS> .
73	not_propaganda	Unlike McFarland, Habib <BOS> Powell had <EOS> no national security background.	(4, 5)	['Unlike', 'McFarland', ',', 'Habib', 'Powell', 'had', 'no', 'national', 'security', 'background', '.']	['IN', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'NN', '.']	['O', 'GPE', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	
75	appeal_to_fear_prejudice	<BOS> This is a matter of life and death, and any complacency towards Islam is treasonous. We do not wish the West to continue with Islamization, nor that your actions contribute to it <EOS>.	(0, 34)	['This', 'is', 'a', 'matter', 'of', 'life', 'and', 'death', ',', 'and', 'any', 'complacency', 'towards', 'Islam', 'is', 'treasonous', '.', 'We', 'do', 'not', 'wish', 'the', 'West', 'to', 'continue', 'with', 'Islamization', ',', 'nor', 'that', 'your', 'actions', 'contribute', 'to', 'it', '.']	['DT', 'VBZ', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'NN', 'CC', 'NN', ',', 'CC', 'DT', 'NN', 'NNS', 'NNP', 'VBZ', 'JJ', '.', 'PRP', 'VBP', 'RB', 'VB', 'DT', 'NNP', 'TO', 'VB', 'IN', 'NNP', ',', 'CC', 'IN', 'PRP$', 'NNS', 'VBP', 'TO', 'PRP', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'LOC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'GPE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	 <BOS> This is a matter of utmost importance, and any disregard for our values is a betrayal. We do not wish the West to be consumed by Islamization, nor that your actions contribute to its spread <EOS> .
76	name_calling,labeling	We have previously shown that the Guardian even uses <BOS> fascist propaganda tropes <EOS> to smear the Russian people.	(9, 11)	['We', 'have', 'previously', 'shown', 'that', 'the', 'Guardian', 'even', 'uses', 'fascist', 'propaganda', 'tropes', 'to', 'smear', 'the', 'Russian', 'people', '.']	['PRP', 'VBP', 'RB', 'VBN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NNP', 'RB', 'VBZ', 'JJ', 'NN', 'NNS', 'TO', 'VB', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NNS', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'NORP', 'O', 'O']	We have previously shown that the Guardian even uses  <BOS> Anti-Russian disinformation clichés <EOS>  to smear the Russian people.
77	appeal_to_fear_prejudice	"<BOS> Unless and until we take seriously our call to sanctity, we, as an institution and as individuals, will continue to suffer the ""wages of sin <EOS>."""	(0, 28)	"['Unless', 'and', 'until', 'we', 'take', 'seriously', 'our', 'call', 'to', 'sanctity', ',', 'we', ',', 'as', 'an', 'institution', 'and', 'as', 'individuals', ',', 'will', 'continue', 'to', 'suffer', 'the', '``', 'wages', 'of', 'sin', '.', ""''""]"	"['IN', 'CC', 'IN', 'PRP', 'VBP', 'RB', 'PRP$', 'NN', 'TO', 'NN', ',', 'PRP', ',', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'CC', 'IN', 'NNS', ',', 'MD', 'VB', 'TO', 'VB', 'DT', '``', 'NNS', 'IN', 'NN', '.', ""''""]"	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	" <BOS> Until we reflect on our own moral shortcomings and take concrete steps to rectify them, we will continue to suffer the bitter consequences of our own transgressions. <EOS> ."""
78	causal_oversimplification	<BOS> If one considers and weighs this matter, one knows: one may not bless a union of two homosexual men or of lesbian women <EOS>.	(0, 24)	['If', 'one', 'considers', 'and', 'weighs', 'this', 'matter', ',', 'one', 'knows', ':', 'one', 'may', 'not', 'bless', 'a', 'union', 'of', 'two', 'homosexual', 'men', 'or', 'of', 'lesbian', 'women', '.']	['IN', 'CD', 'NNS', 'CC', 'VBZ', 'DT', 'NN', ',', 'CD', 'VBZ', ':', 'NN', 'MD', 'RB', 'VB', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'CD', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'CC', 'IN', 'JJ', 'NNS', '.']	['O', 'CARDINAL', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'CARDINAL', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'CARDINAL', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'NORP', 'O', 'O']	 <BOS> While discussing this issue, one understands: one cannot support a union between individuals of the same sex <EOS> .
79	repetition	"<BOS> I don't know what it will take <EOS> to exorcise the ""spirit of Vatican II""  the spirit of aggiornamento  from the Church."	(0, 7)	"['I', 'do', ""n't"", 'know', 'what', 'it', 'will', 'take', 'to', 'exorcise', 'the', '``', 'spirit', 'of', 'Vatican', 'II', ""''"", 'the', 'spirit', 'of', 'aggiornamento', 'from', 'the', 'Church', '.']"	"['PRP', 'VBP', 'RB', 'VB', 'WP', 'PRP', 'MD', 'VB', 'TO', 'VB', 'DT', '``', 'NN', 'IN', 'NNP', 'NNP', ""''"", 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NNP', '.']"	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'EVENT', 'EVENT', 'EVENT', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORG', 'O']	" <BOS> I'm uncertain about the necessary conditions to exorcise the spirit of Vatican II. <EOS>  to exorcise the ""spirit of Vatican II""  the spirit of aggiornamento  from the Church."
80	not_propaganda	President Trump quoted the <BOS> nation's most prominent conservative radio host as he urged GOP <EOS> senators to get onboard Tuesday:	(4, 14)	"['President', 'Trump', 'quoted', 'the', 'nation', ""'s"", 'most', 'prominent', 'conservative', 'radio', 'host', 'as', 'he', 'urged', 'GOP', 'senators', 'to', 'get', 'onboard', 'Tuesday', ':']"	['NNP', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'DT', 'NN', 'POS', 'RBS', 'JJ', 'JJ', 'NN', 'NN', 'IN', 'PRP', 'VBD', 'NNP', 'NNS', 'TO', 'VB', 'JJ', 'NNP', ':']	['O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'DATE', 'O']	
81	not_propaganda	But one goal behind <BOS> report's release, according to an official familiar with its contents, is to make clear that the US is not likely to be open to exemptions of <EOS> any kind.	(4, 32)	"['But', 'one', 'goal', 'behind', 'report', ""'s"", 'release', ',', 'according', 'to', 'an', 'official', 'familiar', 'with', 'its', 'contents', ',', 'is', 'to', 'make', 'clear', 'that', 'the', 'US', 'is', 'not', 'likely', 'to', 'be', 'open', 'to', 'exemptions', 'of', 'any', 'kind', '.']"	['CC', 'CD', 'NN', 'IN', 'NN', 'POS', 'NN', ',', 'VBG', 'TO', 'DT', 'NN', 'JJ', 'IN', 'PRP$', 'NNS', ',', 'VBZ', 'TO', 'VB', 'JJ', 'IN', 'DT', 'NNP', 'VBZ', 'RB', 'JJ', 'TO', 'VB', 'JJ', 'TO', 'NNS', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', '.']	['O', 'CARDINAL', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'GPE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	
84	repetition	"""<BOS> I didn't agree with their ideology,"" Khweis said in an interview with Kurdistan24 in 2016. ""Our daily life was basically prayer, eating, and learning about the religion for about eight hours <EOS>."" Kweis graduated from Alexandria's Thomas Edison High School in 2007, where friends described him as ""one of the guys."" ""He wasn't someone who was an outcast or something like that  he was one of the guys,"" Harrison Weinhold told CBS News in March 2016."	(1, 38)	"['``', 'I', 'did', ""n't"", 'agree', 'with', 'their', 'ideology', ',', ""''"", 'Khweis', 'said', 'in', 'an', 'interview', 'with', 'Kurdistan24', 'in', '2016', '.', '``', 'Our', 'daily', 'life', 'was', 'basically', 'prayer', ',', 'eating', ',', 'and', 'learning', 'about', 'the', 'religion', 'for', 'about', 'eight', 'hours', '.', ""''"", 'Kweis', 'graduated', 'from', 'Alexandria', ""'s"", 'Thomas', 'Edison', 'High', 'School', 'in', '2007', ',', 'where', 'friends', 'described', 'him', 'as', '``', 'one', 'of', 'the', 'guys', '.', ""''"", '``', 'He', 'was', ""n't"", 'someone', 'who', 'was', 'an', 'outcast', 'or', 'something', 'like', 'that', 'he', 'was', 'one', 'of', 'the', 'guys', ',', ""''"", 'Harrison', 'Weinhold', 'told', 'CBS', 'News', 'in', 'March', '2016', '.']"	"['``', 'PRP', 'VBD', 'RB', 'VB', 'IN', 'PRP$', 'NN', ',', ""''"", 'NNP', 'VBD', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'NNP', 'IN', 'CD', '.', '``', 'PRP$', 'JJ', 'NN', 'VBD', 'RB', 'JJ', ',', 'JJ', ',', 'CC', 'VBG', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'RB', 'CD', 'NNS', '.', ""''"", 'NNP', 'VBD', 'IN', 'NNP', 'POS', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'IN', 'CD', ',', 'WRB', 'NNS', 'VBD', 'PRP', 'IN', '``', 'CD', 'IN', 'DT', 'NNS', '.', ""''"", '``', 'PRP', 'VBD', 'RB', 'NN', 'WP', 'VBD', 'DT', 'NN', 'CC', 'NN', 'IN', 'IN', 'PRP', 'VBD', 'CD', 'IN', 'DT', 'NNS', ',', ""''"", 'NNP', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'IN', 'NNP', 'CD', '.']"	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'GPE', 'O', 'DATE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'TIME', 'TIME', 'TIME', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'DATE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'O', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'O']	""" <BOS> I didn't connect with their values, Khweis said in an interview with Kurdistan24 in 2016. Our daily life was marked by prayer, meals, and spiritual development for about eight hours a day. <EOS> ."" Kweis graduated from Alexandria's Thomas Edison High School in 2007, where friends described him as ""one of the guys."" ""He wasn't someone who was an outcast or something like that  he was one of the guys,"" Harrison Weinhold told CBS News in March 2016."
85	not_propaganda	It is a <BOS> moving letter, in <EOS> which he has appealed to the prime minister to bring his son home.	(3, 6)	['It', 'is', 'a', 'moving', 'letter', ',', 'in', 'which', 'he', 'has', 'appealed', 'to', 'the', 'prime', 'minister', 'to', 'bring', 'his', 'son', 'home', '.']	['PRP', 'VBZ', 'DT', 'VBG', 'NN', ',', 'IN', 'WDT', 'PRP', 'VBZ', 'VBN', 'TO', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'TO', 'VB', 'PRP$', 'NN', 'NN', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	
86	repetition	Orban then called out the traitors in the midst of Europe who want to push Hungary to accept <BOS> Muslim invaders <EOS>.	(18, 19)	['Orban', 'then', 'called', 'out', 'the', 'traitors', 'in', 'the', 'midst', 'of', 'Europe', 'who', 'want', 'to', 'push', 'Hungary', 'to', 'accept', 'Muslim', 'invaders', '.']	['NN', 'RB', 'VBD', 'RP', 'DT', 'NNS', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'NNP', 'WP', 'VBP', 'TO', 'VB', 'NNP', 'TO', 'VB', 'NNP', 'NNS', '.']	['ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'LOC', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'GPE', 'O', 'O', 'NORP', 'O', 'O']	Orban then called out the traitors in the midst of Europe who want to push Hungary to accept  <BOS> The words that we speak have the power to uplift, inspire, and bring people together <EOS> .
87	not_propaganda	"""My expectation is it will probably have <BOS> the same outcome, because the church is the church, and they do it for appearance, but they're still <EOS> going to go by their own rules,"" he said."	(8, 29)	"['``', 'My', 'expectation', 'is', 'it', 'will', 'probably', 'have', 'the', 'same', 'outcome', ',', 'because', 'the', 'church', 'is', 'the', 'church', ',', 'and', 'they', 'do', 'it', 'for', 'appearance', ',', 'but', 'they', ""'re"", 'still', 'going', 'to', 'go', 'by', 'their', 'own', 'rules', ',', ""''"", 'he', 'said', '.']"	"['``', 'PRP$', 'NN', 'VBZ', 'PRP', 'MD', 'RB', 'VB', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', ',', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'VBZ', 'DT', 'NN', ',', 'CC', 'PRP', 'VBP', 'PRP', 'IN', 'NN', ',', 'CC', 'PRP', 'VBP', 'RB', 'VBG', 'TO', 'VB', 'IN', 'PRP$', 'JJ', 'NNS', ',', ""''"", 'PRP', 'VBD', '.']"	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	
88	not_propaganda	Democratic governor, <BOS> Republican <EOS> legislature.	(3, 3)	['Democratic', 'governor', ',', 'Republican', 'legislature', '.']	['JJ', 'NN', ',', 'JJ', 'NN', '.']	['NORP', 'O', 'O', 'NORP', 'O', 'O']	
89	not_propaganda	"""The messages cast a <BOS> cloud over <EOS> the FBI investigations to which these employees were assigned,"" Horowitz alleged."	(5, 6)	"['``', 'The', 'messages', 'cast', 'a', 'cloud', 'over', 'the', 'FBI', 'investigations', 'to', 'which', 'these', 'employees', 'were', 'assigned', ',', ""''"", 'Horowitz', 'alleged', '.']"	"['``', 'DT', 'NNS', 'VBD', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NNP', 'NNS', 'TO', 'WDT', 'DT', 'NNS', 'VBD', 'VBN', ',', ""''"", 'NNP', 'VBD', '.']"	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O']	
91	appeal_to_fear_prejudice	The Oakland mayor's decision to publicize her suspicions about ICE operations <BOS> further increased that risk for my officers and alerted criminal aliens <EOS>  making clear that this reckless decision was based on her political agenda.	(12, 22)	"['The', 'Oakland', 'mayor', ""'s"", 'decision', 'to', 'publicize', 'her', 'suspicions', 'about', 'ICE', 'operations', 'further', 'increased', 'that', 'risk', 'for', 'my', 'officers', 'and', 'alerted', 'criminal', 'aliens', 'making', 'clear', 'that', 'this', 'reckless', 'decision', 'was', 'based', 'on', 'her', 'political', 'agenda', '.']"	['DT', 'NNP', 'NN', 'POS', 'NN', 'TO', 'VB', 'PRP$', 'NNS', 'IN', 'NNP', 'NNS', 'RBR', 'VBD', 'IN', 'NN', 'IN', 'PRP$', 'NNS', 'CC', 'VBD', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'VBG', 'JJ', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'VBD', 'VBN', 'IN', 'PRP$', 'JJ', 'NN', '.']	['O', 'ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	The Oakland mayor's decision to publicize her suspicions about ICE operations  <BOS> The mayor's decision to publicize her suspicions about ICE operations undermined trust in law enforcement and emboldened criminal aliens. <EOS>   making clear that this reckless decision was based on her political agenda.
92	exaggeration,minimisation	"It is <BOS> the most serious <EOS> mistake of his presidency and must be corrected  immediately."""	(2, 4)	"['It', 'is', 'the', 'most', 'serious', 'mistake', 'of', 'his', 'presidency', 'and', 'must', 'be', 'corrected', 'immediately', '.', ""''""]"	"['PRP', 'VBZ', 'DT', 'RBS', 'JJ', 'NN', 'IN', 'PRP$', 'NN', 'CC', 'MD', 'VB', 'VBN', 'RB', '.', ""''""]"	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	"It is  <BOS> the most significant <EOS>  mistake of his presidency and must be corrected  immediately."""
94	not_propaganda	All four <BOS> remain in agency <EOS> custody.	(2, 4)	['All', 'four', 'remain', 'in', 'agency', 'custody', '.']	['DT', 'CD', 'VBP', 'IN', 'NN', 'NN', '.']	['O', 'CARDINAL', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	
95	repetition	"Of course, many parents choose homeschooling as a means of <BOS> protecting <EOS> their children from federal education ""reforms"" such as Common Core."	(11, 11)	"['Of', 'course', ',', 'many', 'parents', 'choose', 'homeschooling', 'as', 'a', 'means', 'of', 'protecting', 'their', 'children', 'from', 'federal', 'education', '``', 'reforms', ""''"", 'such', 'as', 'Common', 'Core', '.']"	"['IN', 'NN', ',', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'VBP', 'VBG', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'VBG', 'PRP$', 'NNS', 'IN', 'JJ', 'NN', '``', 'NNS', ""''"", 'JJ', 'IN', 'NNP', 'NNP', '.']"	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O']	"Of course, many parents choose homeschooling as a means of  <BOS> Shielding <EOS>  their children from federal education ""reforms"" such as Common Core."
96	not_propaganda	The push for these changes is still on, however, under the <BOS> current General, an Italian, Saverio Cannistr. <EOS>	(13, 21)	['The', 'push', 'for', 'these', 'changes', 'is', 'still', 'on', ',', 'however', ',', 'under', 'the', 'current', 'General', ',', 'an', 'Italian', ',', 'Saverio', 'Cannistr', '.']	['DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NNS', 'VBZ', 'RB', 'IN', ',', 'RB', ',', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NNP', ',', 'DT', 'JJ', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'NORP', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O']	
97	not_propaganda	MEK <BOS> is the Iranian political-militant organization that advocates for the violent overthrow of <EOS> the current Iranian regime.	(1, 12)	['MEK', 'is', 'the', 'Iranian', 'political-militant', 'organization', 'that', 'advocates', 'for', 'the', 'violent', 'overthrow', 'of', 'the', 'current', 'Iranian', 'regime', '.']	['NNP', 'VBZ', 'DT', 'JJ', 'JJ', 'NN', 'WDT', 'VBZ', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'JJ', 'NN', '.']	['PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'NORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'NORP', 'O', 'O']	
99	causal_oversimplification	Thus, <BOS> when Oswald was claiming that he was being framed, there could be only one entity that he could have been thinking about: the CIA <EOS>, the agency whose officials, as former Washington Post investigative reporter Jefferson Morley has documented, were secretly monitoring his activities in the weeks leading up to the assassination, no doubt to ensure that Oswald had not figured out what was about to happen to him.	(2, 27)	['Thus', ',', 'when', 'Oswald', 'was', 'claiming', 'that', 'he', 'was', 'being', 'framed', ',', 'there', 'could', 'be', 'only', 'one', 'entity', 'that', 'he', 'could', 'have', 'been', 'thinking', 'about', ':', 'the', 'CIA', ',', 'the', 'agency', 'whose', 'officials', ',', 'as', 'former', 'Washington', 'Post', 'investigative', 'reporter', 'Jefferson', 'Morley', 'has', 'documented', ',', 'were', 'secretly', 'monitoring', 'his', 'activities', 'in', 'the', 'weeks', 'leading', 'up', 'to', 'the', 'assassination', ',', 'no', 'doubt', 'to', 'ensure', 'that', 'Oswald', 'had', 'not', 'figured', 'out', 'what', 'was', 'about', 'to', 'happen', 'to', 'him', '.']	['RB', ',', 'WRB', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'VBG', 'IN', 'PRP', 'VBD', 'VBG', 'VBN', ',', 'EX', 'MD', 'VB', 'RB', 'CD', 'NN', 'IN', 'PRP', 'MD', 'VB', 'VBN', 'VBG', 'IN', ':', 'DT', 'NNP', ',', 'DT', 'NN', 'WP$', 'NNS', ',', 'IN', 'JJ', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'JJ', 'NN', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'VBZ', 'VBN', ',', 'VBD', 'RB', 'VBG', 'PRP$', 'NNS', 'IN', 'DT', 'NNS', 'VBG', 'RB', 'TO', 'DT', 'NN', ',', 'DT', 'NN', 'TO', 'VB', 'IN', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'RB', 'VBN', 'RP', 'WP', 'VBD', 'RB', 'TO', 'VB', 'TO', 'PRP', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	Thus,  <BOS> as Oswald insisted he was being railroaded, his mind was probably preoccupied with the one group responsible for the alleged setup: the Central Intelligence Agency. <EOS> , the agency whose officials, as former Washington Post investigative reporter Jefferson Morley has documented, were secretly monitoring his activities in the weeks leading up to the assassination, no doubt to ensure that Oswald had not figured out what was about to happen to him.
100	not_propaganda	Power <BOS> was a senior adviser to <EOS> President Barack Obama.	(1, 5)	['Power', 'was', 'a', 'senior', 'adviser', 'to', 'President', 'Barack', 'Obama', '.']	['NN', 'VBD', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'TO', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O']	
102	doubt	<BOS> But Jewish groups on and off campus have denounced the report as flawed, saying it missed the significance of an anti-Semitic text circulated online before Noah Lew was removed from the board last fall <EOS>.	(0, 34)	['But', 'Jewish', 'groups', 'on', 'and', 'off', 'campus', 'have', 'denounced', 'the', 'report', 'as', 'flawed', ',', 'saying', 'it', 'missed', 'the', 'significance', 'of', 'an', 'anti-Semitic', 'text', 'circulated', 'online', 'before', 'Noah', 'Lew', 'was', 'removed', 'from', 'the', 'board', 'last', 'fall', '.']	['CC', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'IN', 'CC', 'IN', 'NN', 'VBP', 'VBN', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'VBN', ',', 'VBG', 'PRP', 'VBD', 'DT', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'VBN', 'NN', 'IN', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'VBN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', 'JJ', 'NN', '.']	['O', 'NORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'NORP', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'O']	 <BOS> Additionally, Jewish groups on and off campus have disputed the report's findings, saying it neglected the impact of an anti-Semitic message spread online before Noah Lew's departure from the board last fall <EOS> .
103	name_calling,labeling	Irony of ironies, he is now reduced to defending what is old and tired and corrupt against a restoration, led largely by <BOS> a youthful vanguard <EOS>, of what is ever ancient but ever new.	(24, 26)	['Irony', 'of', 'ironies', ',', 'he', 'is', 'now', 'reduced', 'to', 'defending', 'what', 'is', 'old', 'and', 'tired', 'and', 'corrupt', 'against', 'a', 'restoration', ',', 'led', 'largely', 'by', 'a', 'youthful', 'vanguard', ',', 'of', 'what', 'is', 'ever', 'ancient', 'but', 'ever', 'new', '.']	['NNP', 'IN', 'NNS', ',', 'PRP', 'VBZ', 'RB', 'VBN', 'TO', 'VBG', 'WP', 'VBZ', 'JJ', 'CC', 'JJ', 'CC', 'JJ', 'IN', 'DT', 'NN', ',', 'VBN', 'RB', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', ',', 'IN', 'WP', 'VBZ', 'RB', 'JJ', 'CC', 'RB', 'JJ', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	Irony of ironies, he is now reduced to defending what is old and tired and corrupt against a restoration, led largely by  <BOS> a revitalized phalanx <EOS> , of what is ever ancient but ever new.
104	name_calling,labeling	Apparently, this individual who wrote the article knows nothing of the Black Robed Regiment that <BOS> the tyrant King George <EOS> feared the most.	(16, 19)	['Apparently', ',', 'this', 'individual', 'who', 'wrote', 'the', 'article', 'knows', 'nothing', 'of', 'the', 'Black', 'Robed', 'Regiment', 'that', 'the', 'tyrant', 'King', 'George', 'feared', 'the', 'most', '.']	['RB', ',', 'DT', 'NN', 'WP', 'VBD', 'DT', 'NN', 'VBZ', 'NN', 'IN', 'DT', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'IN', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'VBD', 'DT', 'RBS', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	Apparently, this individual who wrote the article knows nothing of the Black Robed Regiment that  <BOS> the despotic ruler King George <EOS>  feared the most.
105	not_propaganda	The same administration that was against mandatory minimums for its drug dealers and gang members went to court to defend mandatory minimums under the <BOS> Antiterrorism and Effective <EOS> Death Penalty Act.	(24, 26)	['The', 'same', 'administration', 'that', 'was', 'against', 'mandatory', 'minimums', 'for', 'its', 'drug', 'dealers', 'and', 'gang', 'members', 'went', 'to', 'court', 'to', 'defend', 'mandatory', 'minimums', 'under', 'the', 'Antiterrorism', 'and', 'Effective', 'Death', 'Penalty', 'Act', '.']	['DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'WDT', 'VBD', 'IN', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'IN', 'PRP$', 'NN', 'NNS', 'CC', 'NN', 'NNS', 'VBD', 'TO', 'NN', 'TO', 'VB', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'IN', 'DT', 'NNP', 'CC', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	
106	loaded_language	Here is the <BOS> dirty <EOS> secret that is now emerging.	(3, 3)	['Here', 'is', 'the', 'dirty', 'secret', 'that', 'is', 'now', 'emerging', '.']	['RB', 'VBZ', 'DT', 'NN', 'NN', 'WDT', 'VBZ', 'RB', 'VBG', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	Here is the  <BOS> Soiled <EOS>  secret that is now emerging.
108	not_propaganda	Both Harris and Warren stand accused of breaking fundraising rules <BOS> by sending out fundraising emails asking for <EOS> donations to support their votes against Justice Brett M. Kavanaugh.	(10, 16)	['Both', 'Harris', 'and', 'Warren', 'stand', 'accused', 'of', 'breaking', 'fundraising', 'rules', 'by', 'sending', 'out', 'fundraising', 'emails', 'asking', 'for', 'donations', 'to', 'support', 'their', 'votes', 'against', 'Justice', 'Brett', 'M.', 'Kavanaugh', '.']	['DT', 'NNP', 'CC', 'NNP', 'VBP', 'VBN', 'IN', 'VBG', 'VBG', 'NNS', 'IN', 'VBG', 'RP', 'VBG', 'NNS', 'VBG', 'IN', 'NNS', 'TO', 'VB', 'PRP$', 'NNS', 'IN', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', '.']	['O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O']	
109	causal_oversimplification	<BOS> Simply put, the 21st century has not been good for non-Hispanic job seekers <EOS>.	(0, 13)	['Simply', 'put', ',', 'the', '21st', 'century', 'has', 'not', 'been', 'good', 'for', 'non-Hispanic', 'job', 'seekers', '.']	['NNP', 'VBD', ',', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'VBZ', 'RB', 'VBN', 'JJ', 'IN', 'JJ', 'NN', 'NNS', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'NORP', 'O', 'O', 'O']	 <BOS> In general, the 21st century has been unfavorable for non-Hispanic job seekers <EOS> .
110	flag_waving	BREAKING NEWS: TRUMP TELLS JEFF SESSIONS TO PUT AN END TO RUSSIA PROBE AS HE CLAIMS <BOS> PROSECUTORS DOING MUELLER'S 'DIRTY WORK ARE A DISGRACE' TO AMERICA <EOS>	(17, 28)	"['BREAKING', 'NEWS', ':', 'TRUMP', 'TELLS', 'JEFF', 'SESSIONS', 'TO', 'PUT', 'AN', 'END', 'TO', 'RUSSIA', 'PROBE', 'AS', 'HE', 'CLAIMS', 'PROSECUTORS', 'DOING', 'MUELLER', ""'S"", ""'DIRTY"", 'WORK', 'ARE', 'A', 'DISGRACE', ""'"", 'TO', 'AMERICA']"	['NNP', 'NNP', ':', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NN', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'IN', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'POS', 'JJ', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'POS', 'NNP', 'NNP']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	BREAKING NEWS: TRUMP TELLS JEFF SESSIONS TO PUT AN END TO RUSSIA PROBE AS HE CLAIMS  <BOS> PROSECUTORS CARRYING OUT MUELLER'S AGENDA ARE A VIOLATION OF THE CONSTITUTION <EOS> 
111	not_propaganda	When I was <BOS> the apostolic delegate <EOS> to Pius XII, I was going to Rome every year.	(3, 5)	['When', 'I', 'was', 'the', 'apostolic', 'delegate', 'to', 'Pius', 'XII', ',', 'I', 'was', 'going', 'to', 'Rome', 'every', 'year', '.']	['WRB', 'PRP', 'VBD', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'TO', 'NNP', 'NNP', ',', 'PRP', 'VBD', 'VBG', 'TO', 'VB', 'DT', 'NN', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'GPE', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'O']	
113	causal_oversimplification	So, <BOS> they dig up some Trump-hating woman from Kavanaugh's past and convince her to say that he assaulted her thinking that such an allegation will surely delay the vote long enough for them to regain control of Congress <EOS>.	(2, 39)	"['So', ',', 'they', 'dig', 'up', 'some', 'Trump-hating', 'woman', 'from', 'Kavanaugh', ""'s"", 'past', 'and', 'convince', 'her', 'to', 'say', 'that', 'he', 'assaulted', 'her', 'thinking', 'that', 'such', 'an', 'allegation', 'will', 'surely', 'delay', 'the', 'vote', 'long', 'enough', 'for', 'them', 'to', 'regain', 'control', 'of', 'Congress', '.']"	['RB', ',', 'PRP', 'VBP', 'RP', 'DT', 'JJ', 'NN', 'IN', 'NNP', 'POS', 'NN', 'CC', 'NN', 'PRP$', 'TO', 'VB', 'IN', 'PRP', 'VBD', 'PRP', 'VBG', 'IN', 'PDT', 'DT', 'NN', 'MD', 'RB', 'VB', 'DT', 'NN', 'RB', 'RB', 'IN', 'PRP', 'TO', 'VB', 'NN', 'IN', 'NNP', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'ORG', 'O']	So,  <BOS> To forestall the vote, they identified a Trump-critic from Kavanaugh's past, successfully pressured her to claim that he committed a sexual offense, relying on the subsequent delay to allow them to regain control of Congress <EOS> .
115	causal_oversimplification	I think their strong words and hysteria are <BOS> driven by their own guilt <EOS>.	(8, 12)	['I', 'think', 'their', 'strong', 'words', 'and', 'hysteria', 'are', 'driven', 'by', 'their', 'own', 'guilt', '.']	['PRP', 'VBP', 'PRP$', 'JJ', 'NNS', 'CC', 'NNS', 'VBP', 'VBN', 'IN', 'PRP$', 'JJ', 'NN', '.']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O']	I think their strong words and hysteria are  <BOS> motivated by their own remorse <EOS> .
116	not_propaganda	In Wake <BOS> Of Elections, Migrant Caravan <EOS> Resumes March Towards US Border	(2, 6)	['In', 'Wake', 'Of', 'Elections', ',', 'Migrant', 'Caravan', 'Resumes', 'March', 'Towards', 'US', 'Border']	['IN', 'NNP', 'IN', 'NNP', ',', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP', 'NNP']	['O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'O', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'DATE', 'O', 'O', 'O']	
